A Guide to the Papers of Edythe C. Harrison 1961-1993
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Campaign Files
  - Campaign for the United States Senate 1984
    - Farmers Union Farm Bureau (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Farm-Rural Virginia, Inc. materials (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Cooperative Farmer-Correspondence (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Federal Workers and Federal Retirees (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Federal Pensions (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Federal Employees [2 yellow folders] (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Federal Election Commission Wall Street Journal Article (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Film Industry Issues (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Federal Deficit-M.C. Reed (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Firefighters-Norfolk Firefighters' Journal June 1984 (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Flannery Literature-10th Congressional District Race (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Foreign Policy-articles and materials (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Policy-Mondale Speeches (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Free Trade-AIPAC (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Funeral Directors (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Gay Rights [court rulings] (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Hampton Roads (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Pro-Handgun Control (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Gary Hart Briefing Materials (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Health-Hart Materials (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Draft Health Care Paper (Mary Evans) (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Health Care (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Health Care Medicare (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Helms (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Hollings Model Brochure (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Housing Bensley Project-Chesterfield (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Housing for Low-Income (Box-folder Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Human Rights-Soviet Jewry (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Industrial Policy (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Information Access to Goverment Information-Restrictions Imposed by Reagan (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Informed Consent-articles and materials (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Israel (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 5)
    - State Senator Jim Jones Newsletter May 1984 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Labor-Mondale Speeches (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Labor-Pierce Issues Letter (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Liberal Groups (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Abraham Lincoln-Douglas (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Medicare-Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Medicare-Senator Kennedy Statement (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Middle East Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Middlesex Report Feb. & May 1984 (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Issues (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Hart Military Reform Materials (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Military Spouses (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Military-Procurment "Spare Parts Catalog" (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Military Waste (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Military Wives I (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Military Wives II (Box-folder Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Harris Miller Briefing Materials (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Miller Campaign Literature (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Mondale Stump Speech (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 3)
    - National Airport Center for Urban Education Materials (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 4)
    - National House Democratic Caucus (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 5)
    - NARFE (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Newport News Shipyard (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 7)
    - New Options Newsletter (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Northern Virginia Issues (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Voter Options on Nuclear Arms Policy (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear Security Speech-Gary Hart (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Nuclear Arms (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Nuclear Power Industry (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Nuclear Winter: Marvin Schelgel-Virginia Beach (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Nunn Materials on NATO July 19, 1984 (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Nurse Practioners Information (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Nuts and Bolts at the Pentagon-A Spare Parts Catalog (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Total Action Against Poverty-TAP (Box-folder Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Poverty Articles on Hunger Legislation (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Poverty Entitlement Program Articles (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Poverty-Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Poverty-Democratic Policy Committee Report on President Reagan (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Poverty-Washington Post Editorial May 6, 1984 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Poverty-Hunger Project Materials (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Prisons and Crimes-Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Research Help (fr:DSCC) (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Republican Platform Critique (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Republican Platform (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Restitution Sentencing (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Rural Coalition Materials (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Older Virginians-Luther Stringham (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Olin (6th Congressional District) Press Releases (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Olympic Boycott Articles (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Political Action Committees (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Sabato Article on Virginia Senate Race 1982 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 18)
    - School Prayer-articles and materials (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Schroeder-family/fairness materials (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 20)
    - SELIG Correspondence (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Senate Votes 1984 (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Senior Citizens (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Sisisky News Releases (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Small Business (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Social Security-Articles and Materials (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Social Security-NEA Policy Paper (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Speech-Biden stump speech (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Steel (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Taxes Position Clips (Box-folder Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Tax (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Tax Policy (Center for Community Change) (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Tax Policy Effects on Regan Cuts (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Tidewater Issues (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Title IX (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Tobacco (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Tourism-Robb Press Releases (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Trade Remidies Act (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Trade (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Transportation Issues (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Transportation-Pierce Materials (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Policy Committee-Unemployment (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Uranium Mines in Virginia I (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Uranium Mines in Virginia II (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Veterans-Hart Materials (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Action Report January 1984 (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Facts (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Department of Health (Box-folder Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Voting Records United States Senate (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 1)
    - George Washnington Farewell Address Warning of Military Complex (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Wilderness-Bill Boucher Materials (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Wilderness Issues-James Loesel (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Wolf Correspondence August 8, 1984 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Women-National Business Woman Magazine June/July 1984 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Women's Issues-Insurance Discrimination (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Women-Equality Issues (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Women-Democratic Policy Issues (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Women-Impact of Reagan Budget March 1984 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Women's Issues Divorce Laws (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Women: John Glenn Position Paper (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Women's National Democratic Club-Democratic Platform Materials (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Women's Equity Action League-Legislative Report (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Women's Issues-Mondale Materials (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Women's Campaign Fund (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Women (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 17)
    - World Future Society-Edie White Materials (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Senate Campaign Clippings and News Releases 1984
    - Clippings November 1983 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Clippings December 1983 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Clippings 1983 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Clippings I: January 1984 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Clippings II: January 1984 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Clippings February 1984 (Box-folder Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Clippings March 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Clippings April 1-6 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Clippings April 7-19 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Clippings April 20-30 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Clippings I: May 1-7 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Clippings II: May 1-7 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Clippings I: May 8-14 1984 (Box-folder Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Clippings II: May 8-14 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Clippings May 5-17 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Clippings May 18 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Clippings May 19 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Clippings May 20 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Clippings I: May 21-31 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Clippings II: May 21-31 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Clippings I: June 1-11 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Clippings II: June 1-11 1984 (Box-folder Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Clippings June 12-30 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Clippings July 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Clippings August 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Clippings September 1, 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Clippings I: October 1-7 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Clippings II: October 1-7 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Clippings October 25-31 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Clippings November 1-6 1984 (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Assorted Clips I (Box-folder Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Assorted Clips II (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Washington Post U.S. Senate Election 1978 (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous-Election I: 1984 (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous-Election II: 1984 (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous-Election III: 1984 (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Debate Clips Washington Post-Election 1984 (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Clips I (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Clips II (Box-folder Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings I (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings II (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings III (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings IV (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings V (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings VI (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings VII (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings VIII (Box-folder Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings IX (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings X (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XI (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XII (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XIII (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XIV (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XV (Box-folder Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XVI (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings XVII (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clips 1980-1984 (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Chase City Sun (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Farmville Herald (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Alexandria Gazette (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Alexandria Journal (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Arlington Journal (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Ashland Herald Progress (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Bristol Herald Courier (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Bristol Virginia-Tennessean (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Bull Mountain Bugle (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Charlottesville Daily Progress (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Christiansburg News Messenger (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Coalfield Progress (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Convington Virginian (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Culpeper Star-Exponent (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Danville Register (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Fairfax Journal (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Fauquier Democrat (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Fredericksburg Freelance-Star (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Fincastle Herald (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Galax Gazette (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Harrisonburg Daily News Record (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Hopewell News (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Lynchburg Daily Advance (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Manassas Journal Messenger (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Martinsville Bulletin (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Newport News Daily Press (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Newport News Times Herald (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Norfolk Virginian Pilot (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Northern Virginian Sun (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Northumberland Echo (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Petersburg Progess-Index (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Potomac News (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Pulaski Southwest Times (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Rappahanock Record (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Rappahanock Times (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Richmond News Leader (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Roanoke Times & World News (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Radford News Journal (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 41)
    - South Boston News & Record (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Strasburg Northern Virginian Daily (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Staunton Leader (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Suffolk News-Herald (Box-folder Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Newspaper Clippings-1984 Election I 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings-1984 Election II 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings-1984 Election III 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings-1984 Election IV 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings June & July 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Press Clippings August & September 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings October & November 1984 (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Warner-"Style" Section (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Detroit News (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 10)
    - "The Vriginia Democrats" (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 11)
    - National Taxpayers Union (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Democratic National Convention-San Francisco (Box-folder Box 60, Folder 13)
    - To Be Clipped I (Box-folder Box 61, Folder 1)
    - To Be Clipped II (Box-folder Box 61, Folder 2)
    - To Be Clipped III (Box-folder Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Richmond Times-Dispatch and Virginia-Pilot November 7, 1984 (Box-folder Box 61, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings I (Box-folder Box 61, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings II (Box-folder Box 61, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings I (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings II (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings III (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings IV (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings V (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings VI (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings VII (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings VIII (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings IX (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings X (Box-folder Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Edythe Harrison 1961-1978 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Edythe Harrison 1979-1980 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Edythe Harrison 1981-1983 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Senate Campaign January-June 1984 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Senate Campaign July-December 1984 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Edythe Harrison 1987-1994 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings re: Edythe Harrison n.d. (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 8)
- Virginia Opera Association
  - Correspondence (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 10)
  - MASTERWORK-The Virginia Opera Capital Campaign for the Renovation of the Norfolk Center Theater (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material-Other Opera Companies (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Nominating Committee 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 63, Folder 13)
  - VOA Auction (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Mary Queen of Scots Premier (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Mary Queen of Scots (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 3)
  - A Dickens Christmas in Norfolk (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Awards for the Arts (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 5)
  - New Yorker Magazine (Violetta in Virginia pp. 88-93) June 30, 1975 (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Opern Welt, Virginia Opera article pp. 25-26 (German) March, 1998 (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 7)
  - VOA Challenge 1981 (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Harrison Opera House (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 9)
  - 100th Birthday Celebration Luncheon Honoring Eleanor Robson Belmont January 10, 1979 (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Guild Nominating Committee (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Opera Association-Nominating Committee for the Opera Executive Committee (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Opera Programs I (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Opera Programs II (Box-folder Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Opera Programs III (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Materials (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Opera Reviews I (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Opera Reviews II (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Opera Association Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 6)
- General Papers
  - Arts
    - Arts Impact Report of NSCL (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Alliance for Arts Education (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Arts-Speech May 1980 (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Arts-Kennedy Center (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk Commission on the Arts and Humanities, by-laws & Harrison's Reappointment (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Arts in the Corrections (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Education
    - Jobs for Virginia's Graduates (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box-folder Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Speech-Gerrit Knodt "Marketing Vocational Education" (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Legislation Senate Bill #660 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Contacts (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Internal Revenue Service re: Virginia Vocational-Technical Educational Foundation, Inc. (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Vocational-Technical Education Foundation (VWEF) Meeting State Board of Education (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Marion, Virginia Foundation (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Governor Baliles-Formation of VVEF 1987 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Commission on Excellence in Education (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Restated Bylaw June 2, 1989 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Biography [members of the VVEF] (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 10)
    - VVEF Board of Directors 1987-1989 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Criteria for Forming Local Vo-Tech Foundations (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Incoming VVEF Correspondence (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Speech-Edythe Harrison (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Article "Education as Funny Business" Chester E. Finn, Jr. (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Speeches for the 105th Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, Virginia Departtment of Education May 1988 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 16)
    - South Carolinia Forum (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Roy Smith Suggestions (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Richard Rivin, LIFE Inc. (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Resolution State Chamber and Construction Industry (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Ford Quillen-House of Delegates (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Virginia State Goverment-Executive Branch 1986 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Vocational Education in Public Schools (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Career Education Advisory Committee Annual Report 1986-1987 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Virginia State Plan for Vocational Education (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Council of Vocational Education (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Wilder, Lawrence Correspondence (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Prince William Foundation (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 28)
    - City of Virginia Beach-Ambassador, Department of Economic Development, Vol.6 No. 2 July 1989 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases (VVEF) (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Dewey Oakley-Incoming Letters (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 31)
    - News Articles June, July, August 1989 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 32)
    - News Articles, copies (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 33)
    - News Articles, originals (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 34)
    - United States Department of Labor (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Forecast-The Fastest Growing Trades (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Thor Letter to Bailes and Wilder (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Thor Disribution (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Superintendent Memo July 6, 1988 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 39)
    - State Board of Education on Vocational Technical Education 1987 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Speech-Ann McLaughlin (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Minutes-VVEF (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 42)
    - 2000 Youth: A Call to Action 1986 (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Newspaper Articles-VVEF I (Box-folder Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Newspaper Articles-VVEF II (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County Educational Foundation (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Fundraising (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Skill Training I (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Skill Training II (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Workforce 2000 (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Goals-VVEF (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Endorsements and Requests (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 8)
    - John Alison (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Apprenticeship Training (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Executive Director Contract-VVEF (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 11)
    - George Eanes Duties (Box-folder Box 67, Folder 12)